RG 009, Office of the Attorney General
Connecticut State Library
- Series 1. Correspondence, 1899-1947
  - 1946
    - Insurance Department, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Israel Putnam Memorial Camp Ground Commission, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Judicial Department, 1946 (Box 18)
    - L (Miscellaneous), 1946 (Box 18)
    - Labor & Factory Inspection, 1946 (Box 18)
    - Legislative Council, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Library, State, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Liquor Control Commission, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Long Lane School, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Mansfield State Training School & Hospital, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Mediation & Arbitration, State Board of, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Medical Examining Board, State, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Merritt Parkway Commission, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Milk Administrator, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Mosquito Control State Board of, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Motor Vehicles Department, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Mystic Oral School For the Deaf, 1945 (Box 19)
    - N (Miscellaneous), 1946 (Box 19)
    - Natureopathic, Board of, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Norwich State Hospital, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Nurses Examining Board, State, 1946 (Box 19)
    - O (Miscellaneous), 1946 (Box 19)
    - Old Lime - Old Say Brook Bridge Commission, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Opticians Commission, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Osteophatic, Board Of Registration & Examination, 1946 (Box 19)
    - P (Miscellaneous), 1946 (Box 19)
    - Park & Forest Commission, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Personnel Director, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Pharmacy Board, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Police Department State, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Port Survey. Commission, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Prison, Connecticut State, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Public Utilities Commission, 1945-1946 (Box 19)
    - Purchases, Supervisor of, 1946 (Box 19)
    - R (Miscellaneous), 1946 (Box 19)
    - Regional Markets, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Retirement Commission, 1946 (Box 19)
    - S (Miscellaneous), 1946 (Box 19)
    - School For Boys, Connecticut, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Secretary of the State, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Shell Fish Commission, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Soldiers, Sailors, & Marines Fund, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Southbury Training School, 1944-1946 (Box 19)
    - Tax Commissioner, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Teachers Retirement Board, 1945-1946 (Box 19)
    - Traffic Commission, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Treasurer, State, 1945-1946 (Box 19)
    - Tree Protection Examining Board, Connecticut, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Tuberculosis Commission, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Unemployment Compensation Commissioner, 1946 (Box 19)
    - United Nations Organization, 1945-1946 (Box 19)
    - United States Government, 1941-1946 (Box 19)
    - University Of Connecticut, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Veterans’ Home Commission, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Veterans Reeployment & Advisory Commission, 1946 (Box 19)
    - W (Miscellaneous), 1946 (Box 19)
    - Welfare Department, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Welfare Department compromises, 1946 (Box 19)
  - 1947
    - A (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 20)
    - Accountancy, State Board of, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Adjutant General, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Aeronautics Commission, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Agriculture, Department of, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Alcoholism, Commission on, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Architectural Examining Board, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Attorneys General Association, 1947-1948 (Box 20)
    - Attorneys General of Other States, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Auditors, State, 1946-1947 (Box 20)
    - B (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 20)
    - Bank Commissioner, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Beach Erosion Control Commission, Connecticut, 1934-1942 (Box 20)
    - Blind, Board Of Education of, 1947 (Box 20)
    - C (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 20)
    - Chiropractic Examiners, State Board of, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Commissioners of Steamship Terminals Matters, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Compensation Commissioner, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Comptroller, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Connecticut Reformatory - Cheshire, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Connecticut State Hospital, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Contested Elections to House of Representatives, 1946-1947 (Box 20)
    - Council of State Governments, 1947 (Box 20)
    - County Commissioners, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Courts, 1947 (Box 20)
    - D (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 20)
    - Dairy & Food Commission, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Dental Commission, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Development Commission, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Domestic Animal Commission, 1947 (Box 20)
    - E (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 20)
    - Education, State Board of, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Election Matters, 1946-1947 (Box 20)
    - Erosion Control Commission, Connecticut Shore, 1946 (Box 20)
    - F (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 20)
    - Fairfield State Hospital, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Farms & Markets, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Farms & Market, Commission of, 1947-1948 (Box 20)
    - Finance & Control, Commissioner of, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Fish & Game Commission, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Food & Drug Commission, 1947 (Box 20)
    - G (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 20)
    - General Assembly - Bills, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Governor, 1947 (Box 20)
    - H (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 20)
    - Healing Arts, State Board of, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Health Department, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Highway Condemnation Approvals Under $1,000, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Highway Department, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Housing Authority, Connecticut State, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Insurance Department, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Inter-Racial Commission, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Interstate Sanitation Commission, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Israel Putnam Memorial Camp Ground Commission, 1947 (Box 21)
    - J (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 21)
    - Judicial Department, 1947 (Box 21)
    - K (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 21)
    - L (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 21)
    - Labor & Factory Inspection, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Legislative Commissioner, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Legislative Research, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Letters (Under S. 149 GS), 1947 (Box 21)
    - Library, State, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Liquor Control Commission, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Long Lane School, 1947 (Box 21)
    - M (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 21)
    - Mansfield State Training School & Hospital, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Medical Examining Board, State, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Merritt Parkway Commission, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Milk Administrator, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Motor Vehicle Department, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Mystic Oral School for the Deaf, 1947 (Box 21)
    - N (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 21)
    - National Association of Attorneys General, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Natureopathic, Board of, 1946-1947 (Box 21)
    - Norwich State Hospital, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Nurses Examining Board, State, 1947 (Box 21)
    - O (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 21)
    - Old Lime - Old Saybrook Bridge Commission, 1946-1947 (Box 21)
    - Optometry, Board of, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Osteopathic, Board Of Registration & Examination, 1947 (Box 21)
    - P (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 21)
    - Park & Forest Commission, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Personnel Appeal Board, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Personnel Director, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Pharmacy Board, 1938-1947 (Box 21)
    - Police Department, State, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Port Survey Commission, 1946 (Box 21)
    - Prison, Connecticut State, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Prison Association, Connecticut, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Public School Building Commission, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Public Utilities Commission, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Purchases, Supervisor of, 1947 (Box 21)
    - R (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 21)
    - Retirement Commission, 1947 (Box 21)
    - S (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 21)
    - School for Boys, Connecticut, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Secretary of the State, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Shellfish Commission, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Soldiers, Sailors, & Marines Fund, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Southbury Training School, 1947 (Box 21)
    - State Mental Hospitals, Joint Committee of, 1947 (Box 21)
    - Steamship Terminals, Commissioners of, 1947 (Box 22)
    - Superior Court, 1947 (Box 22)
    - T (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 22)
    - Tax Commissioner, 1947 (Box 22)
    - Teachers Retirement Board, 1947 (Box 22)
    - Traffic Commission, 1947 (Box 22)
    - Treasurer, State, 1947 (Box 22)
    - Tree Protection Examining Board, Connecticut, 1947 (Box 22)
    - Tuberculosis Commission, 1947 (Box 22)
    - U (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 22)
    - Unemployment Compensation Commissioner, 1947 (Box 22)
    - United State Government, 1947 (Box 22)
    - University of Connecticut, 1947 (Box 22)
    - University Of Connecticut Bond Commission, 1947 (Box 22)
    - V (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 22)
    - Veterans Administration, 1947 (Box 22)
    - Veterans Bonus, 1946-1947 (Box 22)
    - Veterans Home Commission, 1947 (Box 22)
    - Veterans Reemployment Advisory Commission, 1947 (Box 22)
    - Voting, 1947 (Box 22)
    - W (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 22)
    - Water Commission, State, 1947 (Box 22)
    - Welfare Department, 1947 (Box 22)
    - Welfare Department Compromises, 1947 (Box 22)
    - Welfare Department Uncollectibles, 1947 (Box 22)
    - Y (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 22)
    - Z (Miscellaneous), 1947 (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous documents, 1899-1917 (Box 31)
    File contains correspondence.
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1900-1903 (Box 36)
- Series 2. Case Files, bulk
  - T002854, 0.5 cubic feet
    - The Attorney General of the State of Connecticut v. Albert Levitt, 1929-1931; 4 folders (Box 4)
    - E. Victor Erickson, et al. v. William R. Foote, et al., circa 1930 (Box 4)
    - Connecticut v. McCook, Exr, et al., 1922-1930; 7 folders (Box 4)
    - Connecticut v. Frederick A. Tyrrell, 1923 (Box 4)
    - Connecticut Mutual Life Insurance Co. v. Ernest E. Rogers, et al., 1930 (Box 4)
    - Daniel E. Griswold v. Alling, et al., 1928 (Box 4)
    - Edwin S. Pickett, Pros. Atty. v. Antonio Marcucci's Liquors, 1930 (Box 4)
    - Rollin U. Tyler v. Benjamin W. Alling, 1929 (Box 4)
    - George A. Wilcox v. Town of Madison, et al., 1928 (Box 4)
  - 1984-094, cubic feet
    - Testimony in re - Plymouth Granite Co. vs. State Highway Department, 1928 November; 1 transcript volume (Box 23)
    - Testimony State of Connecticut vs. Windsor Locks and Warehouse Point Bridge and Ferry Company, 1908 April; 1 transcript volume (Box 23)
    - In the Matter of Charges Against Honorable Heman O. Averill, Commissioner on Domestic Animals, Before His Excellency Simon E. Baldwin, Governor, 1912 February; 1 transcript volume (Box 23)
    - Bridgeport Trust Co. v. Board of Equalization, 1929-1931 (Box 24)
    - Novogroski, Max vs. John A. MacDonald, Highway Comm., 1936-1938 (Box 24)
    - Max Novogroski and Charlotte R. Novogroski, et al. against the State of Connecticut, 1935 November 13; 1 transcript volume (Box 24)
    - Max Novogroski against John A. MacDonald, Highway Commissioner, 1936 October 29; 1 transcript volume (Box 24)
    - Testimony in re - Mount Carmel Case, 1928; 1 transcript volume (Box 24)
    - No. 8993, John A. MacDonald, Highway Commissioner vs. Edwin H. Holden, 1937 September 23; 1 transcript volume (Box 24)
    - Rose E. Jeffers, et al. vs. Town of Plymouth, Conn. Highway Commissioner, undated; 1 transcript volume (Box 24)
    - No. 53527, Clossik vs. North Haven, et al., No. 53528, Benson vs. North Haven, et al., 1938 December 13; 1 transcript volume (Box 24)
    - Medical Examining Board, 1927-1933 (Box 25)
      Folder includes correspondence, statements, memorandum, petitions, indictments, findings, and notice of hearing.
    - Attorney General v. Steggins, et al., circa 1922-1931 (Box 25)
      Envelope includes respondents exhibits, petitioners exhibits, and photographs of various grade crossings.
    - Banks and insurance companies, circa 1928 (Box 25)
    - Re Bridgeport Trust Co. appeal, circa 1929-1931 (Box 25)
    - Re Bridgeport Trust Co. appeal - motion, circa 1929-1931 (Box 25)
    - Attorney General vs. Public Utilities Commission (#3), circa 1922-1931 (Box 25)
    - Albert Levitt v. Attorney General, circa 1929-1931 (Box 25)
    - Attorney General vs. Commissioners of the Public Utilities Commission #1179, circa 1911-1931; 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Attorney General vs. Levitt, hearing on petition, 1931 March (Box 26)
    - Warren B. Burrows, Attorney General vs. Richard T. Higgins, et al., Commissioners of Public Utilities Commission of State of Connecticut, 1931 June; 1 transcript volume (Box 26)
    - Attorney General vs. Levitt, 1930-1931 (Box 26)
    - Bridgeport Trust Co., 1928-1930 (Box 26)
    - Manning vs. State, 1934-1938; 3 folders (Box 26)
    - Manning vs. State, circa 1933-1936 (Box 27)
    - Bankers Security Trust, circa 1927-1929 (Box 27)
    - In re. estate of Mary Francis Hopkins, deceased, circa 1903-1904 (Box 27)
    - Estate of George F. Gilman, circa 1904-1905 (Box 27)
    - Arthur F. Eggleston, States Attorney, Ex. Rel. New York Life Insurance Company vs. Theron Upson, Insurance Commissioner, 1905-1906 (Box 27)
    - State of Connecticut vs. United States, circa 1904-1905 (Box 27)
    - Harry L. Beach vs. Thomas D. Bradstreet, Comptroller, 1911-1912 (Box 27)
    - Patrick McGovern vs. Asahel W. Mitchell, Comptroller, and James F. Walsh, Treasurer, circa 1904-1905 (Box 27)
    - Clarence Deming, et al. vs. Thomas D. Bradstreet, Comptroller, and Costello Lippitt, Treasurer, 1911-1912 (Box 27)
    - In re complaint of Henry T. Blake, circa 1899-1904 (Box 27)
    - In re Harriet Andrews Conn. Hospital for Insane, circa 1881-1906 (Box 27)
    - Bank Receivership Files, 1926-1936
      - George J. Bassett, Bank Commissioner vs. Naugatuck Bank & Trust Co., circa 1931-1935; 7 folders (Box 28)
      - Unionville Bank & Trust Co. Michael Glanovsky, Unionville, 1935 (Box 28)
      - The Commercial Trust Co. (L. E. Dary), 1934-1935 (Box 28)
      - Commercial Trust Co. (Franklin L. Lawton, adm. Meyer Zimman vs. Sarah W. Greenstein and Boleslaw Yuskivicz), 1935 (Box 28)
      - Shippee vs. Commercial Trust, 1936 (Box 28)
      - City Bank vs. Cohen, 1935-1936 (Box 28)
      - The Commercial Trust Co. (Selma A. Johnson), 1935 (Box 28)
      - Unionville Bank & Trust Co. (Receivership) closed, 1935-1936 (Box 28)
      - The Windsor Locks Trust and Safe Deposit Co. (Release of Mortgages), 1935 (Box 28)
      - The Windsor Locks Trust and Safe Deposit Co., Perry, Bank Commissioner vs. Barberie, 1935 (Box 28)
      - Bank Commissioner v. The Pawcatuck Bank & Trust Company, 1932-1935 (Box 28)
      - Shippee, Bank Commissioner vs. The Commercial Trust Co., 1935-1936 (Box 28)
      - Savings Bank of New Britain vs. Halloran et al. (Commercial Trust Co.), 1935-1936 (Box 28)
      - Walter Perry, Bank Commissioner, receiver of Commercial Trust Co. re Benjamin Furniture Co., 1935-1936 (Box 28)
      - Lester E. Shippee, Bank Commissioner vs. The Commercial Trust Co. - injunction, 1935-1936 (Box 28)
      - City Bank and Trust Co. lease to Sears, Robuck Company, 1935-1936 (Box 28)
      - Commercial Trust Company, rec. (Quigley, George, et als), 1926-1935 (Box 28)
      - City Bank and Trust Co., 1935 (Box 28)
      - Bassett, Bank Commissioner vs. Unionville Bank & Trust Co., 1935-1936 (Box 28)
      - Travelers Bank - E. F. Manchester et als, 1933-1935 (Box 28)
      - City Bank and Trust Co. (compromises), 1935-1936 (Box 28)
      - City Bank and Trust Co. (receivership) closed, 1935 (Box 28)
      - The City Bank and Trust Company (Cohen foreclosure), 1935-1936 (Box 28)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company - miscellaneous, 1938-1941 (Box 29)
      Accordian file includes Interstate Commerce Commission Finance Dockets; petitions; reports; proceedings; correspondence; memorandums; answers; orders; exhibits; and notices of hearings. The documents appear to be related to the reorginization of the railroad company.
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company exceptions to second plan of reorganization, 1939-1945 (Box 29)
      Accordian file includes Interstate Commerce Commission Finance Dockets; correspondence; notices; and appeals.
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company reorganization, 1921-1946; 1 booklet and 13 folders in 1 accordian file
      - Interstate Commerce Commission Finance Docket No. 10992, 1941; 1 booklet (Box 30)
      - Re New Haven & Northampton Co, 1921-1946 (Box 30)
      - Boston and New York Airline Railroad, 1939-1941; 2 folders (Box 30)
      - New Haven Railroad reorganization. (Supplemental File) re: petition rights of Air Line mortgage, 1936-1945 (Box 30)
      - Miscellaneous, 1937-1940 (Box 30)
        Folder includes an order of notice, petition, correspondence, and Along the Line Annual Report Issue, vol. 10, no. 3, New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad.
      - Mortgage trustee, 1939 (Box 30)
      - New York & Providence & Boston, 1938-1940 (Box 30)
      - Hartford & Connecticut Western Railroad Company (in bankruptcy) (N.H.Rd. reorganization), 1936 (Box 30)
      - Hartford & Connecticut Western Railroad Company, 1940 (Box 30)
      - Stafford Springs Street Railway Company, 1939 (Box 30)
      - Hartford & Connecticut Western Railroad Company, re New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company, 1936-1939 (Box 30)
      - Naugatuck Railroad Company, 1935-1939 (Box 30)
      - Housatonic Railroad Company, 1935-1940 (Box 30)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company reorganization, 1937-1941; 1 accordian file (Box 30)
    - Estate of Justus S. Hotchkiss, 1915-1917 (Box 31)
    - Fox Film Corporation vs. John H. Trumbull, Governor of the State of Connecticut, et al.; American Feature Film Company, Inc. vs. John H. Trumbull, Governor of the State of Connecticut, et al., circa 1925 (Box 31)
    - Merritt Parkway Files
      - Marguerite L. Reid - New Canaan, 1936; Parcel number 1. (Box 32)
      - Hoyt and Dominick - New Canaan, 1936; Parcel number 2B. (Box 32)
      - Charles J. and Freda Wissler - New Canaan, 1934; Parcel number 3. (Box 32)
      - Estate of Ida C. Hoyt - New Canaan, 1933; Parcel number 2. (Box 32)
      - Estate of Mary Waterbury - New Canaan, 1936; Parcel number 4. (Box 32)
      - Dr. Ben S. and Dr. Emily D. Barringer - New Canaan, 1929-1939; Parcel number 5. (Box 32)
      - J. H. and M. A. Haller - New Canaan, 1933; Parcel number 6. (Box 32)
      - Mary L. Miller - New Canaan, 1934; Parcel number 7. (Box 32)
      - Estate of Mary L. Miller - New Canaan, 1936; Parcel number 7B. (Box 32)
      - Carrie L. Jelliff - New Canaan, 1936; Parcel number 8. (Box 32)
      - Mary P. Miller - New Canaan, 1936; Parcel number 9. (Box 32)
      - Calvin G. Miller - New Canaan, 1936; Parcel number 9.5. (Box 32)
      - Lydia B. Gartner - New Canaan, 1933; Parcel number 10. (Box 32)
      - Walter S. and Mary P. Miller - New Canaan, 1933; Parcel number 11. (Box 32)
      - John L. and Viola A. DeForest - New Canaan, 1934; Parcel number 12. (Box 32)
      - John L. and Viola A. DeForest - New Canaan, 1936; Parcel number 12.5. (Box 32)
      - Estate of Cornelius G. Taylor - New Canaan, 1934; Parcel number 14. (Box 32)
      - Jennie E. VanName - New Canaan, 1934-1936; Parcel number 15. (Box 32)
      - Carrie Jones - New Canaan, 1934; Parcel number 15.5. (Box 32)
      - Mabel Wood - New Canaan, 1934-1936; Parcel number 16. (Box 32)
      - Antoinette D. Lapham - New Canaan, 1936; Parcel number 17. (Box 32)
      - Antoinette D. Lapham - New Canaan, 1936; Parcel number 17F. (Box 32)
      - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad - easement - Norwalk; easement and purchase - New Canaan, 1937 (Box 32)
      - B. H., S. P., and F. L. Mead - New Canaan, 1934; Parcel number 18. (Box 32)
      - Augustus M. Gerdes - New Canaan, 1933; Parcel number 19. (Box 32)
      - J. Irene Benedict and Nellie F. Hexamer - New Canaan, 1936; Parcel number 20. (Box 32)
      - Nellie F. Hexamer and J. Irene Benedict - New Canaan, 1934; Parcel number 20. (Box 32)
      - Amelia W. Wyllie - New Canaan, 1933; Parcel number 21. (Box 32)
      - Estate of Elizabeth G. Kiska - New Canaan, 1934; Parcel number 22. (Box 32)
      - Lyman W. and Marguerite I. Young - New Canaan, 1936; Parcel number 24. (Box 32)
      - Edith A. Redfield - New Canaan, 1936; Parcel number 25. (Box 32)
      - Florence D. Preston - New Canaan, 1934; Parcel number 27. (Box 32)
      - Carmine Bucciarelli - New Canaan, 1934-1936; 2 folders; Parcel numbers 28A-E. (Box 32)
      - Joseph and Susan Kery - New Canaan, 1936; Parcel number 29. (Box 32)
      - Giovina Bucciarelli - New Canaan, 1934; Parcel number 30. (Box 32)
      - John Tingets - New Canaan, 1934-1935; Parcel number 31. (Box 32)
      - Frank and Rosie Seckar - New Canaan, 1934; Parcel number 32. (Box 32)
      - Miscellaneous, 1936 (Box 32)
        Folder contains a list of vendors and purchase prices of land; correspondence; and memoroandum.
      - Miscellaneous, 1932-1934 (Box 32)
        Folder contains correspondence.
      - Memos, etc., circa 1933 (Box 32)
        Folder contains notes and memorandum.
      - Sadie Hokunson - Trumbull, 1938-1939 (Box 32)
      - M.J. Realty Co. - Norwalk, 1936; 2 folders; Parcel numbers 3 and 3B. (Box 32)
      - Francis E. Green - Norwalk, 1935-1936; Parcel number 4. (Box 32)
      - Robert E. Kelly - Norwalk, 1934; Parcel number 5. (Box 32)
      - Frank H. Bissell - Norwalk, 1934-1935; Parcel number 6. (Box 32)
      - Thomas E. and Louise H. Powers - Norwalk, 1936-1937; 2 folders; Parcel numbers 7, 7A, and 7B. (Box 32)
      - Florence H. Duffy - Norwalk, 1936; Parcel number 8. (Box 32)
      - John Benn - Norwalk, 1936; Parcel number 9. (Box 32)
      - Anna Benn - Norwalk, 1936; Parcel number 10. (Box 32)
      - Leo and Margaret Heimberger - Norwalk, 1936; Parcel number 11. (Box 32)
      - Augusta M. Finney - Norwalk, 1936; Parcel number 12. (Box 32)
      - Bertha L. Ireland - Norwalk, 1936; Parcel number 13. (Box 32)
      - Mary E. Moody and Orson C. Waterbury - Norwalk, 1936; Parcel number 15. (Box 32)
      - Muriel S. and Leon A. Fish - Norwalk, 1935-1936; Parcel number 16. (Box 32)
      - Norton O. Hurst - Norwalk, 1936; Parcel number 16.5. (Box 32)
      - Rudolph Mayer - Norwalk, 1935-1936; Parcel number 17. (Box 32)
      - Clement and Theresia - Norwalk, 1937; Parcel number 18. (Box 32)
      - David A. and Stella A. Morrissey - Norwalk, 1934-1935; Parcel number 19. (Box 32)
      - Gurczynski condemnation - Norwalk, 1937; Parcel number 20. (Box 32)
      - Mary Marvin Taylor, et al. - Norwalk, 1936; 2 folders; Parcel number 21 and 21B. (Box 32)
      - M. Charles Staack - Norwalk, 1936; Parcel number 22. (Box 32)
      - Norwalk Tire and Rubber Company - Norwalk, 1936; 2 folders; Parcel numbers 23 and 23C-E. (Box 32)
      - Norwalk Tire and Rubber Company - slope rights - Norwalk, 1937 (Box 32)
      - G. CAvanagh - New Canaan and Norwalk, 1936; Parcel number 2. (Box 32)
      - Elizabeth Haller - Norwalk, 1936; Parcel numbers 23.5 and 24. (Box 32)
      - Joseph Scalisi - Norwalk, 1936; 2 folders; Parcel numbers 25 and 25B. (Box 32)
      - City of Norwalk, 1936; Parcel number 25.5. (Box 32)
      - Maurice Friedson - Norwalk, 1934-1935; Parcel number 26. (Box 32)
      - Maurice Friedson - sewer line agreement - Norwalk, 1936 (Box 32)
      - Marie Librizzi - Norwalk, 1936-1937; Parcel number 26.5. (Box 32)
      - Mary A. Ratchford - Norwalk, 1935-1936; 2 folders; Parcel numbers 27, 27B, and 27.25. (Box 32)
      - Estate of Margaret Lucy - Norwalk, 1936; Parcel number 27.5. (Box 32)
      - Alvin D. Wadsworth - Norwalk, 1934-1937; 5 folders; Parcel numbers 28A-28O. (Box 32)
      - Daniel S. Sheehan - Norwalk, 1935; Parcel number 29. (Box 32)
      - William J. Sheehan - Norwalk, 1937; Parcel number 29B. (Box 32)
      - Herman Aaron - Norwalk, 1935; Parcel number 30. (Box 32)
      - Estate of Mary G. Sherwood - Greenwich, 1936; Parcel number 2M. (Box 33)
      - Virginia DeHaven Mixsell - Greenwich, 1936; Parcel number 2.5. (Box 33)
      - William A. Sweeney - Greenwich, 1932-1934; Parcel number 3. (Box 33)
      - Port Green Realty Corp. - Greenwich, 1931-1932; Parcel number 6M. (Box 33)
      - Quentin Twachtman - Greenwich, 1935; Parcel number 8. (Box 33)